let choices = [];
let nameOfChoices = ["A", "B", "C", "D"];
const listOfQuiz = {
    films: [
        {
          question: "The main actor in Titanic is: ",
          choices: [
            "Leonardo Dicaprio",
            "Brad Pitt",
            "Adam Levine",
            "Justin Bieber",
          ],
          answer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "How many chapters does Harry Potter film have? ",
          choices: ["1", "3", "7", "8"],
          answer: "C",
        },
        {
          question: "In the movie Home Alone, where did Kevin get lost in?",
          choices: ["New York", "New Jersey", "Miami", "Chicago"],
          answer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "How many parts does the movie series Fast and Furious have?",
          choiceA: 7,
          choiceB: 8,
          choiceC: 2,
          choiceD: 9,
          answer: "D",
        },
        {
          question: "Who is the villain in the movie Harry Potter?",
          choices: ["Voldemort", "Dumbledore", "Draco Malfoy", "Hagrid"],
          answer: "A",
        },
      ],
      sports: [
        {
          question: "Who is the champion of World Cup 2018?",
          choices: ["France", "Brazil", "Italy", "Germany"],
          answer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "Which football club has the most fans in the world?",
          choices: ["Barcelona", "Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Real Madrid"],
          answer: "C",
        },
        {
          question: "A famous basketball player has just passed away. Who is he?",
          choices: [
            "Kobe Bryant",
            "Michael Jordan",
            "Lebron James",
            "Stephen Curry",
          ],
          answer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the most popular sport in Vietnam?",
          choices: ["Football", "Basketball", "Badminton", "Tennis"],
          answer: "A",
        },
        {
          question: "When is the first time Vietnam won a gold medal in Olympic? ",
          choices: ["2008", "2015", "2016", "2014"],
          answer: "C",
        },
      ],
    }